ADDY: So "Why Does It Always Rain On Me?"
好吧，“你为什么总是向我下雨？”
should probably be the title to this episode.
这应该是本集的标题。
There is a gray cloud coming towards us.
乌云笼罩我们。
MATT: Yeah, so for anyone who doesn't get that,
是的，每个人都不明白，
that's a nice Travis reference.
这是Travis的不错参考
Smooth.
顺利
So this episode is going to be on Travis CI, which
因此，本集将与Travis CI有关
is a super awesome continuous integration tool that ties in
这是一个很棒的超级英雄持续集成工具
very nicely with GitHub.
有了GitHub。
So you literally, like, enable, I
从字面上看，你管理
think it's like a-- you-- I think you're adding a web hook
我认为这就像-您-我认为您正在添加网状犬
or something in Travis.
或特拉维斯的东西。
It's a service you can-- sorry, in GitHub that you add
这是您可以接受的服务-抱歉，您将其添加到GitHub
in to your repo and settings.
在您的设置和仓库中。
And basically whenever you do, like, a commit to a repo
基本上，每次您这样做时，对存储库的承诺
or you do a pull request or anything happens,
或者您要求提款，否则可能会发生什么，
you can set up Travis to perform-- basically set up a VM
您可以安装Travis来执行-或基本上安装VM。
and do whatever you tell it to do.
并命令他想做什么。
ADDY: Yeah, all you need to do is set up
是的，只需安装它。
a Travis YAML configuration file in the root of your projects,
项目库中的Travis YAML设置文件，
and that can be as simple or as crazy as you want to make it.
这可能像您想要的那样简单或疯狂。
MATT: Yeah, I think I was thinking
是的，我想我在想
of the web starter kit, Travis.YAML,
面向初学者的网络捆绑包Travis.YAML，
and it's literally just, like, we
实际上就是我们需要的
need it to run in node four, node five, and that's
在节点4和5上进行管理，仅此而已
all it does.
它做什么。
And then Travis, because it's up for an environment a node,
然后是Travis，因为它对应于节点环境，
it will go, well, I should probably
我会成为，我想我应该
do NPM Install and hope that works.
我安装了NPM，希望它能正常工作。
And then it checks for NPM run tests--
然后他执行NPM测试-
so the NPM script just called "test"--
NPM文本仅称为“测试”-
and it will do whatever it does, and then given that marker,
他会做什么，然后给那个分数，
it returns an exit code of something other than 0.
返回除0以外的任何内容的退出代码。
And then Travis goes, well, the build failed because it
然后特拉维斯出发了，好了，建造失败了
didn't do what you'd expect.
他没有做你想做的。
And it's super handy just having that thing just constantly
保持活动状态非常有用
just checking what the hell you're doing, especially
从地狱所做的一切检查，尤其是
for pull requests, like when you get someone just
对于提款请求，就像有人
give you a load of code and you're
助您一臂之力
like, does this just break everything or does it work?
当您等待时，这会破坏一切还是会起作用？
ADDY: It's just-- it's super useful for keeping everyone
将它保存给所有人非常有用
honest about stuff that they're trying to PR in.
关于PR的明确信息。
It's just great.
太好了
I have some Travis pro-tips.
我有一些使用Travis的专业指导。
MATT: Oh, are they your own, or--
哦，这是您的建议，还是-
ADDY: They came to me vividly in a dream.
它像我梦中的阳光一样来到我身边。
Or a Medium blog post.
或通过发布在博客上。
But, so one of the things we do on a few of our projects
但是，我们在一些项目中所做的一件事情
is we cache our package management directory,
是我们在包目录上运行缓存，
so like our node modules directories.
如节点模块
Some people might cache their [? barrel ?] components
他们中的一些人可能会[鼓？]
as well.
还可以
MATT: It definitely works because you can
之所以有效，是因为您可以
cache any directory, can't you?
he，不是吗？
ADDY: Yeah, pretty much.
是的，戏剧性。
MATT: If there's something you want to generate but then
如果在那里您想生成它，然后
afterwards just keep it around.
您要保留它。
ADDY: Yeah, just speeds up installation having it cached.
是的，它通过在其上执行缓存来加快安装速度。
It's kind of a nice little thing you can do.
您可以做的很好，很简单。
MATT: Yeah.
是的
ADDY: Another optimization is setting your Git checkout
另一个改进是Git验证设置
depths, so that it's only running against the latest
从深处，甚至只能在另一个
commits, for example.
例如，义务。
MATT: Nice.
好漂亮
I think web fundamentals has such a horrific history on Git
我认为该网络的基础知识对Git有着可怕的影响
now by this point that we should probably be using that.
现在，我们应该使用它。
ADDY: I remember using this tool to check out
我记得用这个工具来检查
the largest directories on my system were the other day.
在更大的迹象中，系统又出现了一天。
Web fundamentals checkout was the thickest one.
检查网络基础是否较重。
MATT: Moving on.
我们正在发展。
ADDY: Google engineers know what they're doing.
Google工程师知道他们在做什么。
And my final pro-tip, I think, was just
并指导最后一位专业人员，我认为这是
making sure that you know you can whitelist or blacklist
确保您知道可以将分支机构列入白名单或黑名单，
branches, so that Travis isn't running against everything.
因此，特拉维斯（Travis）并非对所有事情都有效。
If you, for example, have 22 different branches
例如，如果您有22个分支
for Web Starter Kit 2, Matthew.
对于初学者的Grid 2，Matthew。
MATT: Yeah, I should do something about that.
是的，我想我应该为此做些事情。
But the other advantage of that that I was going to add on
但是另一个好处是我要添加
was you can also-- like, Travis adds
还有你，Extras Travis。
a ton of environment variables.
许多环境变量。
So if you've got shell scripts you want to run,
如果您有要运行的设计脚本，
and maybe you want to, like, run certain things on master,
也许您想管理master上的所有内容
but not when there are pull requests or any
但是当有提款要求或
of this other stuff, Travis just dumps a load
特拉维斯（Travis）不会倒货
of environment variables.
环境变量。
Like, one of them is just, like, am I in Travis?
就像其中之一，我在特拉维斯吗？
If I am, do this rather than do it
如果是这样，那就去做而不是去做
if I ran it from a command line or something.
如果从命令行或其他方式运行它。
So that's the other thing that's well worth checking out,
那另一件事，你值得发现，
because these blog posts are just all those things.
因为所有博客文章都是这些东西。
ADDY: So Travis runs really great
特拉维斯的表现非常出色。
when you're trying to get testing done against, like,
当你想测试
Linux or OS X, Windows.
Linux，OS X或Windows
MATT: I don't think it supports Windows,
我认为它不支持Windows，
but there is another service called Appveyor,
但是还有另一项名为Appveyor的服务，
and it has its own equivalent to the Travis YAML.
她在Travis YAML上有补偿
It's slightly different, but largely it's
有点不同，但是总的来说
very, very similar.
都非常相似。
The only gotcha with Appveyor that I found a bit confusing
关于Appveyor的唯一一件事我感到困惑
is it needs a build number for every time it does a run.
每次工作时都需要配置号码
And there's a way you can set it up to auto-increment,
而且总有一种方法可以将其设置为自动递增，
but it's kind of a bit weird the first time you do it.
但这是您第一次使用他有点奇怪
But once you set it up, you're all good to go,
但是一旦准备好，就可以开始工作了，
and it's super handy because it is
这是超自然的，因为
pretty different from a Linux environment.
与Linux环境完全不同。
ADDY: So Appveyor, I found it to be a little bit finicky
承办商，他的祖母需要很多
to get set up pretty consistently,
为了完全一致的安装，
but once that's done, it's just as easy to use as Travis.
但是，一旦设置完成，就可以像Travis一样使用它。
MATT: Yeah, and some of those things you only really to
是的，其中某些事情确实需要完成
have to do it at the start of a project,
在项目开始时，
and then you forget what you've done for the next one, so,
然后忘了你下次做什么
but it's all good.
但是，一切都是完美的。
So then the last thing about that is obviously
最后一件事
when you set these things up is you get a lovely badge
当您证明这些事情是您获得徽章时
to put on your readme.
放入自述文件。
The one last thing I'd mention, because I
我想说的最后一件事，因为我
feel like the tour needs a good shoutout,
我觉得这次巡回演出需要大声喊叫，
is David, which is this year a badge,
大卫，今年的徽章，
and it just tells you whether your dependencies on NPM
它告诉您NPM上的功劳都是
are up to date or not.
是否更新。
That's all it does, but I found it surprisingly helpful
他就是这么做的，但是我发现它非常有用
just for the projects I have just sitting there just going,
仅针对工作清单中的项目，
well, are they up to date?
好吧，他们是最新的吗？
Are they out of date?
老了
What's going on?
怎么了
Yeah, love it.
是的，我喜欢它。
ADDY: Yeah, so people should check that out at david-dm.org.
人们需要在david-dm.org上进行检查。
There's also-- so in the same vein,
在同一条轨道上，
so whenever I'm working on node modules,
当我处理节点模块时，
there's a CLI called David, very similar thing that you can use.
有一个名为David的CLI，可以使用非常相似的东西。
And what that basically does is, again, it
它的基本作用是
will let you know your outdated, like, dev dependencies
它使您知道未发生什么，例如开发人员积分
or outdated dependencies, list them down
或旧信用，将其列出
in the CLI nicely colored, let you know what your version is,
在CLI中以漂亮的颜色确定您的版本，
the latest version is, and it'll also give you,
最新版本是什么，它将为您提供
like, this one-liner you can run to just,
您可以运行的一线
like, instantly bump everything up, which is kind of nice.
它将加速所有操作，非常漂亮。
MATT: Nice.
好漂亮
That is very cool.
太棒了
ADDY: It's just pretty sweet.
太酷了
There's also this thing recently called Greenkeeper.
还有Greenkeeper说话的东西。
Do you remember Greenkeeper?
你还记得Greenkeeper吗？
MATT: Yes, that's the one where it will update everything
是的，它可以更新一切
automatically, run your test suite,
自动运行测试人员，
and if it passes, it will then ping your pull request, going,
如果一切顺利，他会回答您的提款要求，
here you go.
像这样
Just update them,
他在说话
ADDY: Yeah, so people should probably check all of those
是的，人们必须尽一切努力
out.
现在
MATT: If you have good tests, yes.
如果测试不错，是的